https://www.redsquaredb.com/legal/

Legal
Legal & PRIVACY Menu3D ToursAboutProjectsServicesProcessContactVideoJournalLegal PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy has been formulated to assure you of our commitment to your privacy and that of all our clients. It has been prepared to comply with the Data Protection Act. Please CLICK HERE to read our privacy policy.WHO WE AREThis website is owned and managed by Red Square Design & Build Limited, a company incorporated in England and Wales and registered under number 06836252. Red Squares registered office is at Third Floor, 24 Chiswell Street, London, EC1Y 4YXINFORMATION COLLECTED & PURPOSEWe ask you to provide your full name, title, full postal and email addresses. We will process and store this personal information internally only and will not disclose it to third parties. The information gathered is specifically for the purpose of conducting future business with you. Please CLICK HERE to read our cookie policy.AMENDING OR REMOVING YOUR DETAILSYou may amend your details at any time or ask us to remove your details from our files by writing to Red Square, First Floor, Kelly House, Tunbridge Wells, TN1 1YL or emailing Red Square at info@redsquaredb.comCHANGESAny changes made to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this page so as to ensure you are kept informed of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. info@redsquaredb.com+44(0)20 7385 8500This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read More
